Lullaby and goodnight
With roses bedight
With lilies o'er spread
ls baby's wee bed
Tomorrow morn, if God deems
You will wake from your dreams
Good night.
You're it!
One, two, three, four...
Five!
Lukas?
11,12,
13,14,
15,16,
17,18,
19, 20...
Lukas?
GOODNIGHT MOMMY
Mom?
- Morn?
Morn?
That's a fine hello.
Look at your clothes.
Filthy. Take them off right now.
Not here!
Undress by the washing machine.
And then take a shower.
Move it!
There you are.
Thanks.
Lukas wants some too.
Then he can ask me himself.
You only made supper for me.
You know why.
You should apologize.
Am I a person?
- No.
Am I a thing?
- Yes.
Am I a cell phone?
- No.
Am I a pair of pants?
Can you wear me?
- No.
Can you eat me?
Do you need me every day?
- Yes.
Am I hair?
- No.
It's a thing.
That's needed in daily life.
You use it almost every day.
Do I'?
Not by yourself, but...
A car?
- Yes, right.
You got it.
Am I an animal?
- No.
Am I a thing?
Am I a person?
Yes.
Am I a man?
- No.
Am I a woman?
- Yes.
A grown-up?
Am I still alive?
Yes.
Amlon IV?
Am I...
a TV hostess?
Yes.
Am I on German TV?
- No.
Austrian.
Am I famous?
Well, sort of.
Barbara Karlich?
No.
A clue?
You like animals.
Come on!
Another clue.
You have two kids.
How do I know who has two kids?
Do I know the person?
Yes.
Lukas!
That's enough.
That's it.
Come on!
- Mom!
I have something to say.
We were playing!
I don't care.
Dad lets us play.
I don't care what your dad does.
This is important.
I want you to look at me.
So start already.
- Excuse me?
Nothing.
The doctor said I need rest.
And I expect your support.
There'll be some new rules.
I want absolute quiet in the house.
I have to sleep. If it's important,
knock.
And no visitors.
If anyone asks,
Mom is ill.
We'll keep the blinds closed.
I have to avoid sunlight.
You'll play only in the garden, quietly.
Bring nothing inside.
No branches, no animals...
What are you doing?
We'll start over.
Right?
We need to hold this family together.
One from me and one from Lukas.
Very nice.
I'm serious about what I just said.
We won't forget, right?
Good.
It's bedtime now.
Good night.
She's so different.
- Well...
It's just the operation.
You think?
Yeah.
I don't know.
How would you feel
if you'd had an operation like that?
I don't know.
She s not like our mom.
Play it again.
I'm giving you lots and lots of kisses.
I can't wait until I'm back.
Pull the covers up and close your eyes.
Can you count the stars that brightly
Twinkle in the midnight sky?
Can you count the clouds, so lightly
O'er the meadows floating by?
God, the Lord, doth mark their number
With His eyes that never slumber
You He sees and you He loves
Good night.
Get Mom.
Morn?
Lukas?
Hello?
- Hi, good morning.
You sure placed a killer order.
So much, all at once.
Someone having a party?
- No.
Who's all this pizza for?
Pepperoni, pepperoni?
Is that your favorite?
Pepperoni pizza. You must love it.
Yeah.
Bought enough for a year.
There we go, it's all in there.
Open UP-
What in hell...
Since when do we lock doors?
Sorry.
Why is there a lighter in here?
I wanted to burn some books.
Don't act smart.
Get off!
Let him go!
OUR WEDDING
INGRID ULRICH REAL ESTATE -
METTLER HOUSE
FOR SALE: STYLISH RETREAT,
PRICE ON REQUEST
Lukas!
Leg?
Time for your chores!
I've other worries.
I won't play along anymore.
I have to make him stop.
He has to face it.
Wait a second, sorry.
Not here either.
Leg?
Lukas, look.
What's wrong with him?
Leg?
I'm sure it was Mom.
Well?
Fine.
Are you crazy?
Stop that.
What's going on?
What is going on?
We want our mom back.
- What?
Have you gone crazy?
Are you out of your mind?
Clean this up and go to your room!
You're not our mom.
To your room!
Show us your birthmark.
Enough!
- Show us your birthmark.
I've had it.
Anything else, maybe?
I want you to say 10 times
that I'm your mother.
Open up!
- Say it.
You're my mom.
- Properly.
Look at me.
You're my mom, you're my mom...
Louder.
You're my mom.
Stop this foolishness!
I'm not playing along anymore.
Understand?
There'll be only one breakfast
and one set of clothes.
And promise me not to talk
to your brother!
No.
Promise me.
I'm going to get so mad!
Promise me!
Give me your cell. Now!
Stay in your room!
She wants to tear us apart.
Does that hurt?
- No.
Mom, please come back.
I'll do anything you want.
Please come back.
All I wish for is that you'll come
back to us.
Elias?
Trim around your ear.
Here?
Better?
Now we look the same.
Now she won't be able to tell us apart.
It's me. Open the door.
Are we friends?
I'm not mad anymore.
Please open the door.
Well?
Are we friends again?
I have something.
Thanks.
Great, huh?
- Yes.
Can we go outside and try it?
Yes?
What is it?
Can you help us?
Yes.
What's it about?
Are you the priest?
- No, I'm the sexton.
Where's the priest?
He's not here.
Can we call him?
- Yeah.
Sure you can.
Can you come inside
the police station with us?
And talk to the policeman
and explain it to him?
Yeah, no problem.
Open up!
Come out of there! Come out!
Thank you.
Would you like to explain?
It was all a bit much.
The accident. The separation.
What's going on?
Where is our mom?
I'm going insane. Insane.
How do I get up?
You don't.
Where is our mom?
Lukas said, "Where is our mom?"
Untie me now.
No.
It hurts. Untie me.
Tell us where our mom is.
I'm your mom!
No.
Who's she?
Where are the scissors?
Who is she?
A friend.
We always dressed the same.
Who is she really?
Answer.
Please answer.
Hi, I'm from Vienna.
What should I say?
It's my first time doing this.
I like to cook, watch movies.
But I also enjoy spending
the evening watching TV.
Look.
Go away!
Help me.
Stop it!
Stop!
I don't see it.
- What are you doing?
Take another look.
What is this? What is this?
In the video your eyes are brown.
- What?
They're contacts, Christ!
They're in the bathroom.
Why are you lying to me?
I thought we agreed not to believe her.
So? I changed my mind.
Do you believe her, you retard?
You're the retard!
Help!
Where are the damn scissors?
Do you understand? Get the scissors!
Lukas?
Elias...
Sit beside me. Come on.
Come, Elias. Sit here.
Come sit beside me, Elias.
Come on, sit down. So we can talk.
Look.
Elias...
You know I'm your mom.
I can't untie myself.
Just go to the bathroom,
get the scissors and cut me loose.
Nothing bad has happened. Cut me loose.
I want you to say 10 times,
"I won't listen to my brother."
I won't listen to my brother.
I won't...
Louder, please.
I won't listen to my brother.
I won't listen...
I said louder.
Our mom wouldn't do that.
More clearly.
Elias...
I'm sorry.
Again.
I'm sorry, Elias.
Come now.
Please. Cut me loose.
What happened to your nose?
Nothing. Nothing serious.
There, you see?
You'll cut me loose
and I'll make you breakfast.
Cut my feet loose, they hurt.
Lukas?
I know it's hard, but we'll make it.
Come, just cut my feet loose.
Come on, it'll take a sec.
I'll make breakfast.
Just cut it.
That's it.
What are you doing?
There.
What?
What is it?
5&0? -
They had to remove it in hospital.
They're dangerous.
Liar!
They had to. They had no...
Admit that it's a lie.
Just cut me loose, please.
Stop.
Stop!
Tell us where our mom is.
Tell us where our mom is!
It's open.
Hello, Red Cross!
Hello?
Red Cross. Care to make a donation?
Is anybody home?
I'll have a look.
Hello?
Red Cross.
Nobody's there.
It was unlocked, someone must be home.
Hello?
Maybe they're upstairs.
Red Cross.
Hello?
- Hello!
Hello.
Is your mom home?
No, she's not home.
Not upstairs? We heard something.
No, that's our dog.
She's not home?
- No.
It's our dog.
When will Mom be back?
She'll be home soon.
Can we wait?
Where should we wait?
Hand me the list.
I'll see how much we've collected.
The money too?
- Yeah, I'll count it.
Really bad handwriting.
- Yeah.
You'd swear a doctor had written it.
It's barely legible.
Looking forward to school?
Well...
- It starts soon.
Where did you go to school before?
- In Vienna.
A lot more going on there.
We've already collected a tidy sum.
If somebody else gives as much as him,
we'll have done pretty well.
We'll see how much more we get.
What do you do all day?
Not much.
I have to go to the toilet.
Is your mom back?
Not yet.
Is that your own money?
No.
Will your mom be OK with this?
- Yes, I'm sure she will.
She always gives that much.
We don't want any trouble.
You realize that...
We usually don't
accept money from children.
That's a lot of money.
No, we're allowed.
Well, it is a nice house. Just look.
I guess they can afford it.
As a thank-you for the donation,
here's a Band-Aid.
Help!
Help! Help!
Stop! Stop!
Please prove you're our mom.
Ask her what my favorite song is.
What's Lukas' favorite song?
Lullaby and Good Night?
Don't!
Can you count the stars that brightly
Twinkle in the midnight sky?
Can you count the clouds, so lightly
O'er the meadows floating by?
God, the Lord, doth mark their number
With His eyes that never slumber
You He sees and you He loves
Where's our mom?
Don't you know when you
have to pee?
We're not changing them.
Hello?
Untie me.
Now change the bed.
Take off the sheets.
Come on, take them off.
Elias?
Where's our mom?
Elias, come here.
Where is she?
Fine.
Elias, let's make a deal.
I'll play along again.
I'll talk to Lukas again.
Lukas will be alive.
I'll make you both breakfast,
put out your clothes.
We'll do things, like before.
But you have to believe me
that I'm your mom.
You won't really do that.
I promise.
Elias...
It's not your fault Lukas died.
The accident wasn't your fault.
Do you really believe her?
She's lying.
Let her prove she's our mom.
What am I doing?
What's Lukas doing?
But I can't see him!
What's he doing?
Elias...
Mom would know that.
Mom could see him.
She'd know what he's doing.
No, Elias. Don't!
Elias, don't!
Elias, do you hear me?
Help! Help!
God, the Lord, doth mark their number
With His eyes that never slumber
You He sees and you He loves